Guide to the Women on the Job Records WAG.240
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Women on the Job Records
1968-2006
1982-1993
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Women on the Job
McCormick, Lillian
WAG.240
11.5 Linear Feet in 11 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
Women on the Job (WOJ) was founded in 1981 as a private, not-for-profit advocacy organization dedicated to achieving women's equality in the workplace on Long Island. WOJ was a project of Resources for Program Development, Inc. (RPD), which had been established with funding from the North Shore Unitarian Universalist Society VEATCH Program. The WOJ program was initiated in October 1981 by co-founders Lillian McCormick and Charlotte Shapiro. Its mission was to foster equal employment opportunities for women and combat workplace discrimination against women in Long Island communities. The group worked to promote awareness of gender issues at work and in schools, to lobby for and monitor enforcement of relevant laws, to support the principle of equal pay for work of equal value, and to offer training in sexual harassment prevention. Activities included community organizing, coalition building, advocacy, counseling, research, information and referral services and the publication of resource materials. The WOJ Task Force was formed in 1982 as an outgrowth of WOJ, and provided a monthly forum for diverse women to unite, network and respond to employment challenges and problems affecting working women in the Long Island community. WOJ closed its offices in 2006. The collection includes correspondence, files on community organizations and their relations with WOJ, files relating to WOJ programs and projects, brochures, guides, studies, surveys, contact lists, mailings, press releases, publications and reference material on pay equity, sexual harassment, women as public employees, employment discrimination in general, and related legislation.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Lillian McCormick (executive director) on behalf of Women on the Job, in 2005. The accession numbers associated with this gift are 2005.010 and 2014.123.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
Women on the Job (WOJ) was founded in 1981 as a private, not-for-profit advocacy organization dedicated to achieving women's equality in the workplace on Long Island. WOJ was a project of Resources for Program Development, Inc. (RPD) and was supported financially by individual members, corporate sponsors, fundraising events and grants. RPD itself had been established with funding from the North Shore Unitarian Universalist Society VEATCH Program. The WOJ program was initiated in October 1981 by co-founders Lillian McCormick and Charlotte Shapiro. Its mission was to foster equal employment opportunities for women and combat workplace discrimination against women in Long Island communities. The group worked to promote awareness of gender issues at work and in schools, to lobby for and monitor enforcement of relevant laws, to support the principle of equal pay for work of equal value, and to offer training in sexual harassment prevention. Women on the Job programs included community education, community organizing, coalition building, advocacy, counseling, research, information and referral services, and the publication and distribution of information concerning women's employment and employment opportunities on Long Island. The group's constituency included individual women, women's groups, and public, private and not-for-profit employers, including women and men.
The WOJ Task Force was formed in 1982 as an outgrowth of WOJ, and was a major project of the program. The Task Force met monthly, providing a forum for diverse women to unite, network and respond to employment challenges and problems affecting working women in the Long Island community. The coalition advocated for improvement in employment policies and practices affecting women and, more broadly, for legislation that protected working families. Membership was open to all organizations interested in promoting equitable employment practices and opportunities for women in the Long Island area.
The Task Force provided a number of services in the Long Island workplace for both employees and employers, including: a forum in which women facing unfair employment practices could safely report their complaints, obtain information, develop stronger advocacy skills, and obtain referrals to appropriate enforcement agencies and legal advocates. The group provided speakers and distributed newsletters to educate the public about the concerns of working women, and disseminated information on pay equity, race and gender equality on the job, the opening of non-traditional jobs to women (including both blue-collar trades and technical jobs), and ending pregnancy discrimination. It also worked to assure that lawmakers and law enforcers fulfilled their commitments in the area of equal employment opportunities for women.
WOJ participated in a number of projects to support employment equality for women including: the Working Smarts Education Program, the Working Smarts for Teenagers Program, the Coalition to Advocate for Women of Color in Education, and Sexual Harassment Prevention and Training Workshops. The organization produced and distributed a number of publications, including newsletters, reports, and a manual relating to employee equity projects at the local community level, Working for Pay Equity, which was distributed to more than 40 states. WOJ closed its offices in 2006, when some of its functions and programs were taken up by, or merged with, other organizations.
Scope and Content Note
Series I: Minutes, 1983-2006, is comprised of minutes of meetings of the WOJ Task Force Coalition group; relevant correspondence, meeting handouts, agendas, and other material relating to issues discussed at these meetings is also included in this series.
Series II: General Files, 1968-2006, includes a variety of materials concerning WOJ activities and administration, files on organizations and topics of interest to WOJ, individuals and groups affiliated with or in contact with WOJ, and events sponsored by WOJ or the WOJ Task Force. Materials include correspondence and informational documents concerning community organizations and their relations with WOJ. Files relating to WOJ programs and projects include brochures, guides, studies, surveys, contact lists, mailings, and workshop materials. The series also includes WOJ press releases and publications and files of reference material collected by WOJ concerning pay equity, sexual harassment, women as public employees, employment discrimination in general, and related legislation.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically.
The files are grouped into 2 series:
Missing Title
I, Minutes, 1983-2006
II, General Files, 1968-2006
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2630 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Publications (documents); Surveys (documents).; Guidebooks.; Minutes (administrative records); Administrative records.; Fliers (printed matter); Correspondence.; Nassau County (N.Y.).; Suffolk County (N.Y.); Gender discrimination.; Civil rights.; Affirmative Action programs.; Sexual harassment.; New York (N.Y.).; Sexual harassment |x Prevention.; Employment discrimination.; Pay equity.; Women on the Job Task Force; North Shore Unitarian Universalist Society (Plandome, N.Y.); Resources for Program Development; McCormick, Lillian; Shapiro, Charlotte; Women on the Job; McCormick, Lillian
- Series I: Minutes, 1983-2006.
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: Task Force, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Series II: General Files, 1968-2006.
  - Adelphi University Clerical Strike, Dec 13, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Advisory Council, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Affirmative Action Manual, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - American Association of School Administrators: Reports on Women and Minorities in School Administration, Jul 1982, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - American Association of University Women (AAUW), 1987-1991, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - American Business Women's Association (ABWA), 1983, undated, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU): Women's Rights, 1979-1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organization (AFL-CIO), 1981-1986, 2000, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1985, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Anniversary Gala (25th Anniversary), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Annual Holiday Brunch, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Annual Reports, 1984-2004 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Association for Union Democracy, 1982-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Background and Purpose Statements, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Berndt, Cheryl: Nassau Community College, 1984-1985, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bureau of National Affairs, Inc.: The Comparable Worth Issue, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Brandwein, Ruth A.: Presentation, Mar 13, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Brochures, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Center for Multiculturalism in Education: Program Directory Questionnaire, 1988, 1992, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Center for Multiculturalism in Education: Women Helping Girls Conferences, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Center for Women in Government, 1979, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Center for Women in Government: Pay Equity: A Guide for Local Governments in NY State, Feb 1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Center for Women in Government: Suffolk County Pay Equity Study, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Center for Women in Government: Train the Trainer Conference, Nov 1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Center for Women Policy Studies: Harassment and Discrimination Study, Jul 7, 1981-Jul 9, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Central Islip Centers Clericals: Pay Equity, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Central Nassau's Staff Training Day, Jun 5, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Certificates and Letters of Appreciation, 1984-1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1983-1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Classification Study: University of Maine and L.A. School, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Clerical Upgrading Committee, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Clippings: General, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Clippings: General, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Clippings: General, 1990-1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), 1985-1988, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Coalition to Advocate for Women of Color in Education (CAWCE), 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Coalition to Advocate for Women of Color in Education, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Coalition to Advocate for Women of Color in Education: Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Coalition to Advocate for Women of Color in Education: Multicultural Resume Bank, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Coalition to Advocate for Women of Color in Education: Proposed Actions and Progress Reports, 1991-1993, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Coalition to Advocate for Women of Color in Education: Resources, 1981, 1989-1992, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Coalition to Advocate for Women of Color in Education: Statistics, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Clerical Employees, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Commission of Human Rights, City of New York: Sexual Harassment, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Communication Workers of America (CWA), Jan 12, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Community Team Meeting, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Complaints of Discrimination: Intake/Survey Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Complaints of Discrimination: Intake/Survey Forms, 1988-1989, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Conference Samples, 1992-1992 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Contacts List, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, May 1984-Jul 1984 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1984-Dec 1984 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1985-May 1985 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1985-Oct 1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1987-Jul 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Defense Contract Administration Services Region, 1984-1987, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Dinapoli Proposal, Feb 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Directory: Role Models for Non-Traditional Jobs, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Directory Requests, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Discrimination in Employment: General, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - East Hills Elementary School: Sexual Harassment Workshop, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Educational Support Staff Association, 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Employment Research: WOJ Questionnaire, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1983, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Equal Pay Day, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Excellence and Equity in Education Conferences, 1991-1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Facts for Women(WOJ), 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Family Medical Leave Act, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Farmingdale, NY: Sexual Harassment Policy, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Financial Assistance Opportunities, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Ford Proposal, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Foundations: NY State Directory, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Freeport High School: Sexual Harassment, 1988-1992, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fundraising: Susan Isaac Lunch, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Fundraising Brochure, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Gender Equity in Education, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Gender Equity Workshop, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Glen Cove School District, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Grant Application: Chemical Bank, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Grant Proposal: Women in the Long Island Economy, circa 1982 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - He Works, She Works: Gender Stereotype Flyer, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Head Start Day Care Strike, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Help with Employee Resources Program (H.E.R.) Proposals, 1985, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Hempstead, NY: Sexual Harassment Policy, 1992-1993, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Hempstead, NY: Sexual Harassment Policy Managers Training, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Hempstead, NY: Sexual Harassment Policy Material from Eben Breed, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Hempstead, NY: The Mother's Center Development Project, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Hofstra Cultural Center: Conference on Long Island Women Activists and Innovators, Mar 22, 1996-Mar 23, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Hofstra University: Women, Gender and Business, Aug 24, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Honorary Support Invite, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Hospital Samples and Medical Workers, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hotel Workers, 1985, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - How to Check Your Workplace for Sex Discriminatory Practices, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Information Packet, 1991-1992, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Multicultural Education, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Job Evaluation Methods, 1985-1998, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Job Opportunities for Women, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Labels, 1993, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Lanier Worldwide, Inc., 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - League of Women Voters of New York State, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Legal Contracts, 1990, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Legislation, 1989-1992, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Legislation, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Civil Rights Act of 1990, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Economic Equity Act, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Family and Medical Leave Act of 1989, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Lobbying, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: NY Pay Equity, Jan 22, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: NY Pay Equity, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: Sachem, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: Schools and Gender Equity, 1990, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: Sex Equity in Education, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Legislative Grants, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Legislative Task Force on Domestic Violence, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Librarians: Pay Equity, 1982-1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Litigation: Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Lobbying Information, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Long Island Apprenticeship Training Programs, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Long Island Association of Educational Secretaries, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Long Island Center for Workers' Rights, 1988, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Long Island Coalition for Fair Broadcasting, INC. correspondence with Lillian McCormick, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Long Island Coalition for Full Employment, 1982, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Long Island Coalition for Women in Non-Traditional Occupations, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Long Island Community Foundation, 1988-1989, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Long Island: "County Government on Long Island: Employment Patterns of Women" (WOJ report, by L. McCormick and C. Shapiro), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Long Island: Employment of Women in County Government, 1983, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Long Island Fund for Women and Girls, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Long Island Guide: Training Resources(WOJ), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Long Island Midwifery Service, 1981-1987 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Long Island Network of Women Artists, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Long Island Progressive Coalition, 1984-1985, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Long Island Public Schools: Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Long Island Public Schools: Women in Administration Comparison, 1982-1987 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Long Island School Districts: Staff Association Survey "Pay Equity in Contract Negotiations", 1989 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Long Island School Districts: Survey of Clericals and Custodians, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Long Island School Districts: Survey of Employment Applications, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Long Island Technical Assistance Center (LITAC), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Long Island University: C.W. Post Campus, 1994-1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Long Island Women Coalition, Inc., 1986 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Long Island Women in Public School Administration, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Long Island Women's Council for Equal Education, Training and Employment, 1989-1991, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Long Island Women's Institute, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Long Island Workforce Statistics, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Long Island Workplace: Survey of Family Support Policies, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Long Island's Women Agenda: The Agenda, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Members List, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Memo from Women on the Job, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Minority Women in Education, 1990, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Minority Women: Employment, 1976-1988 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Morris, Phillip Proposal, 1988, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Ms. Foundation for Women, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Narrowing the Wage Gap: Conference on Fair Wages for Office Workers, Mar 1985-Apr 1985, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Narrowing the Wage Gap: Conference III, May 9, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Narrowing the Wage Gap: Conference IV for Women on Pay Equity, Apr 16, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Nassau and Suffolk Counties: Questions for County Candidate's Meetings, Nov 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Nassau and Suffolk Counties: Survey of Employment Applications, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Nassau Citizens Budget Committee, 1974-1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Nassau Community College, 1983-1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nassau Community College: Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Nassau Community College: Discrimination Cases, 1984-1985, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Nassau Community College: Helen J. Sisserson, 1983-1985, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Nassau Community College: Sexual Harassment Training, Jan 7, 1987, Jan 14, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Nassau Community College: Susan L. Peragallo, 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Nassau Community College: Workshop on Sexual Harassment, Apr 2, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Nassau County: Affirmative Action (I), 1983-1987, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Nassau County: Affirmative Action (II), 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Nassau County: Board of Cooperative Educational Services (BOCES), 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Nassau County: Budget and It's Impact on Women's Employment Services, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Nassau County: Civil Service Workers Pay Equity, 1983-1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Nassau County: Clippings, 1984-1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Nassau County: CSEA/AFSCME v. Nassau County, 1983-1990, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Nassau County: CSEA/AFSCME v. Nassau County Advocacy at Budget Hearings, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Nassau County: CSEA/AFSCME v. Nassau County Data, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Nassau County: CSEA/AFSCME v. Nassau County Press, 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Nassau County: CSEA/AFSCME v. Nassau County WOJ Advocacy, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Nassau County: Civil Service Commission, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Nassau County: Data on Exempt Women, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Nassau County: Data on Women in Government Departments, 1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Nassau County: Day Care Council, 1983-1988, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Nassau County: EE04 Employment Data, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Nassau County: Equal Pay Lawsuit, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Nassau County: George Sinnott, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Nassau County: Human Rights Commission, 1977-1984 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Nassau County: Labor Market Survey Presentation, Jul 12, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Nassau County: Office of Women's Services, 1993, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Nassau County: Pay Equity Campaign, 1989-1995 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Nassau County: Pay Equity Research Data, 1981-2000, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Nassau County: Police Department, 1981-1989 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Nassau County: Selected Departments Analysis of Women Employees, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)